Next up is where we introduce the entertainment industry's sparkling gemstones Uncovering
続いてはエンタメ業界の輝く宝石をご紹介 明らかにする
This morning is the artist who became a popular topic due to his high toned voice
今朝はハイトーンボイスで話題になったアーティスト
Let's pay attention to his singing together
一緒に彼の歌声に注目しましょう
♫ We watched fireworks blooming in a flash of light ♫
♫ 光の中に咲く花火を見ました♫
♫ Surely this summer is far from over ♫
♫ きっと今年の夏はまだまだ終わらない♫
The person singing the currently popular song >
今話題の曲《FIREWORKS》を歌っている人
Is not DAOKO-san, but a male singer
DAOKOさんじゃなくて男性シンガーです
Futhermore,
さらに、
♫ What happens if my thoughts for you overflows? ♫
♫君への思いが溢れたらどうなる?
♫ When is the right moment or right time ♫
♫ 適切な瞬間または適切な時期はいつですか ♫
♫ To hold your hand? ♫
♫手を握る？ ♫
He is the one with the fresh crsip voice, Mafumafu-san
爽やかなシャキシャキ声のまふまふさんです
His voice has no added autotune
彼の声にはオートチューンが追加されていません
In this year's June, his singing was shown to the 35.000 people that attended his concert at Seibu Dome
今年の6月、西武ドームでのコンサートに参加した35,000人の観客に彼の歌声が披露されました。
♫ Won't you dance with me? ♫
♫一緒に踊りませんか？ ♫
♫ Ripples on the water that resound with sorrow ♫
♫哀しみに響く水面の波紋♫
♫ In the depths of the Yellow River ♫
♫黄河の奥深くで♫
P: I really like him! I listen to his songs everyday! -
P: 私は彼が本当に好きです!毎日彼の歌を聴いています！ -
P: He can sing a high key that girls even sing up to -
P: 彼は女の子でも歌えるハイキーを歌うことができます -
P: The fact that he can make those high notes is astonishing -
P: 彼があの高音を出すことができるという事実は驚くべきことです -
Mafumafu-san,
まふまふさん、
Is actually a very shy person
実はとてもシャイな人
Mafumafu in a shy tone: I'm Mafu
照れた口調でまふまふ：まふです
Because he doesn't show his face,
顔を出さないので、
He keeps his mask on even when we interviewed him
取材中もマスクをしたまま
What kind of artist is Mafumafu?
まふまふってどんなアーティスト？
Let us uncover his charm
彼の魅力を解き明かそう
Now is when ZIP finds the hot topic influencers / Uncovering
今こそZIPが話題のインフルエンサーを見つける時 / Uncovering
Mafumafu-san started posting covers and other videos in 2010
まふまふさんは2010年からカバー動画などの投稿を開始
His total views are over 800 million
総再生回数は8億回以上
It's his first time participating in a TV interview as an individual
テレビの取材に個人で参加するのは初めて
M: Mafumafu, I: interviewer
M:まふまふ、I:インタビュアー
M: I was really nervous; I didn't sleep much last night
M: とても緊張しました。昨夜はあまり眠れなかった
M: so I was really looking forward to it
M: とても楽しみにしていました
M: My replies may not be very serious, sorry about that
M: 私の返事はあまり真剣ではないかもしれません、ごめんなさい
I: What's the reason to not show your face?
I: 顔を出さない理由は何ですか?
M: Because the activities I do are all on the internet,
M: 活動は全部ネット上なので、
M: I'm a bit scared to overly present who I am
M: 私は自分が誰であるかを過度に提示するのが少し怖いです.
The shy Mafumafu-san,
シャイなまふまふさん、
One of his most prominent features being spread accross the internet is his high-toned voice
インターネット上で広まっている彼の最も顕著な特徴の 1 つは、彼の甲高い声です。
Singing at the same field of high notes as female singers
女性歌手と同じ高音域で歌う
♫ A dream within a dream, or an unfullfilled dream ♫
♫ 夢の中の夢 叶わぬ夢 ♫
♫ An orphan and a child neglected by their papa ♫
♫ パパに捨てられた孤児と子供♫
♫ The stars shine brighter the darker the night sky ♫
♫ 星は夜空が暗いほど明るく輝く♫
I: Why can your voice reach so high?
I: なぜあなたの声はそんなに高く届くのですか?
M: Before, I thought that I couldn't reach such a high note
M: 以前は、そんなに高い音は出せないと思っていました
M: Then I thought "Can I reach it?" So I tried to reach it
M: それで、「届くかな？」と思いました。だからたどり着いてみた
M: And then I reached it
M: そして、たどり着いた
Praised along with his natural high-toned voice in his original lyrics
自作歌詞で自然な甲高い声とともに絶賛
M: I've continuing to learn expressions,
M: 表現を学び続けていますが、
M: Even though it's a bit embarrasing to say,
M: ちょっと恥ずかしいけど、
M: But I like reading the reference books used for modern lterature
M: でも、現代文学の参考書を読むのは好きです
M: I brought a lot of books,
M: 本をたくさん持ってきて、
M: and I found that I couldn't understand any of it
M: そして、私はそれのどれも理解できなかったことがわかりました
M: Whether day or night, I'm learning
M: 昼夜を問わず、私は学んでいます
♫ Won't you dance with me? ♫
♫一緒に踊りませんか？ ♫
♫ Ripples on the water that resound with sorrow ♫
♫哀しみに響く水面の波紋♫
♫ In the depths of the Yellow River ♫
♫黄河の奥深くで♫
♫ Dreams of longing are ♫
♫憧れの夢は♫
♫ ephemeral bubbles from a time already past ♫
♫ 過ぎ去った時からの儚い泡 ♫
First of all, the vocals
まずはヴォーカル
It's really like a girl's voice
本当に女の子の声みたい
Because it's usually low
普通に低いから
♫ For whom shall I blossom for ♫
♫誰のために咲こうかな♫
He also knows how to wtite and arrange
彼はまた、加筆とアレンジの方法も知っています
I don't think he's learned it before, stuff like writing songs
彼は以前にそれを学んだとは思わない、曲を書くようなこと
He's a talented person
彼は才能のある人だ
When he closed his knees with a "kyu ('Cute' in Japanese)"
「きゅー」と膝を組むと、
You can tell that his personality is also pretty good
性格もかなり良いのがわかります
Doing his live activities as well as song postings,
ライブ活動はもちろん、楽曲投稿も行い、
He'll continue to work hard on his music carrer
彼はこれからも音楽キャリアを頑張っていきます